[Home](https://www.sensorykidstore.com/ "Home") » [Privacy policy](https://www.sensorykidstore.com/service/privacy-policy/)

Privacy policy
==============

**Please read this Privacy Statement each time BEFORE using this website, as it may change.  
**READING THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT IS THE ONLY NOTICE OF ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT. By further entering and using this website, you agree to the privacy terms, conditions and disclaimers below and as they may be changed from time to time. If you do not wish to be bound by these privacy terms, conditions and disclaimers, you should not access or use this website.

#### Comments and Postings:

We value your input and would like to encourage our customers and other website users to share reliable information or content appropriate thoughts. We reserve the right to post excerpts from online forums, postings and comments on our website, citing the person’s first name or online username (if available) and City, State. Posting comments and other materials to this website is done at your own risk.  Sensory Kids®, LLC / DBA The Sensory Kids® Store DISCLAIMS any liability for use of comments or postings by third parties.

#### Accounts:

Where the website allows you to set up an account, you are agreeing to provide true and accurate information to the best of your knowledge. You are solely responsible for the use of your account and the upkeep of any passwords, usernames, contact, shipping, payment and billing and other required information.

#### Payment Security:

Your information is received through a secure server with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption.

#### We Do Not Sell/Trade/Share Personal Information:

We respect your privacy and do not sell, trade or share your personal information. Sensory Kids®, LLC / DBA The Sensory Kids® Store reserves the right to change this policy, and notice of the change is given by an update of this provision. PLEASE CHECK THIS PROVISION upon using this website to determine if you want to continue the use of this website.

#### Information We Collect To Better Serve You:

Sensory Kids®, LLC / DBA The Sensory Kids® Store reserves the right to collect names, contact information, demographic information and other information relative to surveys and to better identify customer needs and provide better service. We use the information for internal record keeping and communicating with you. We also may use "cookies" to follow web traffic and help us see which pages customers use more than others or to store information you choose to share to simplify your website visit. You can adjust the settings on your computer to accept or decline "cookies".  

#### Links to Other Websites:

We have no control over other websites and DISCLAIM any privacy protection and securities once you link to another website.

Our products
------------

Gift Cards  [Buy Now](https://www.sensorykidstore.com/gift-cards/)

Recently viewed [Clear](https://www.sensorykidstore.com/recent/clear/ "Clear")
------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Loading...
